Secret Service is a drama, war film directed by Hugh Ford.
Lewis Dumont, a Northern officer in the American Civil War, works undercover behind Confederate lines in an
attempt to lead Southern forces away from an area in which a Northern attack is planned.
But Dumont falls in love with a Southern girl and when she proves
useful to his plan, his conscience begins to tear at him.
Major Lewis K. Dumont, played by Robert Warwick.
Edith Varney, played by Wanda Hawley.
General Harrison Randolph, played by Theodore Roberts.
Mrs. Varney, played by Edythe Chapman.
Lieutenant Howard Varney, played by Raymond Hatton.
Wilfred Varney, played by Casson Ferguson.
Secret Service is a lost 1919 American silent American Civil War drama
film starring Robert Warwick and directed by Hugh Ford.
It was produced by Famous Players–Lasky and distributed by Paramount Pictures.
Based on the play Secret Service by William Gillette (New York, 5 Oct
1896), it was remade as a talking picture by RKO in 1931.
One of the story’s chief plot twists is referenced in the 1923 short story "Devil
Cat", featuring Carroll John Daly’s hard boiled detective Race Williams.
The tone is emotional.